{
    "id": "877750298a5f4b23855e3850f5b350dd",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The teacher ...................... the lesson yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teaches",
                "taught",
                "has taught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c5841291ab24278b7a9a93f36497c14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now he ...................... questions to see if the students have understood the lesson.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asks",
                "is asking",
                "asked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a2795e4460c4ff4a3b66dbf1cc42fb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "As he ....................... not satisfied with the answers, he .....................â€¦ the lesson tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is, will repeat",
                "was, would repeat",
                "is, repeated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f4a04a48c77b4782aeb72469e23ad288"
        },
        {
            "question": "John ..................... in hospital for two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is lying",
                "lies",
                "has been lying"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3511a28d6683422aa9243155e167aa40"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ..................... him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were visiting",
                "visited",
                "have visited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4dbf189dd54d4bfabdb17361c6496640"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................... completely.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "recovers",
                "recovered",
                "has recovered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5a62d613b5f24a14af5768c176c6ac7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most probably he ..................... to school next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will come",
                "would come",
                "has come"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6cdd1e3d487e4933b02f3e03ee07b6e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark ........................... for jobs ever since he passed his examination in March.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has applied",
                "has been applying",
                "applied"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc2f838d95524d60a0842d02c0e58486"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last month he .................... for an interview.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has appeared",
                "appeared",
                "was appearing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b44d3bc38ab4f4da61e8ed046ac9593"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................... for the results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waits",
                "is waiting",
                "waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ecfd992b6354df6ba4e7ef645457102"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................. to my friend a fortnight ago inviting her to spend the holidays with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have written",
                "wrote",
                "was writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dff0c7bc1d3f48568cf0d400b7c24f11"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday, I ....................... her reply.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was receiving",
                "received",
                "have received"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25f2c8f2bade475ba1b2e9c25e91c638"
        }
    ]
}